330
0101	Possible arm leads reversed, check lead requested
0102	ARTIFACT PRESENT
0103	CANNOT ANALYZE ECG
0104	ELECTRODE(S) DETACHED ...  Repeat ECG is requested
0201	-- Analysis based on intrinsic rhythm
1002	Marked rhythm irregularity, possible non-conducted PAC, SA block, AV block, or sinus pause
1100	Sinus rhythm
1102	Sinus arrhythmia
1108	Marked sinus arrhythmia
1120	Sinus tachycardia
1130	Sinus bradycardia
1200	Atrial rhythm
1210	Atrial fibrillation
12101	Atrial fibrillation with rapid ventricular response
12102	Atrial fibrillation with slow ventricular response
12103	Atrial fibrillation with aberrant conduction, or ventricular premature complexes
12108	Atrial fibrillation with rapid ventricular response with aberrant conduction, or ventricular premature complexes
12109	Atrial fibrillation with slow ventricular response with aberrant conduction, or ventricular premature complexes
1220	Rapid atrial rhythm
1250	Atrial flutter
12503	Atrial flutter with aberrant conduction, or ventricular premature complexes
12505	Cannot rule out atrial flutter
12506	Atrial fibrillation or flutter
12507	Atrial fibrillation or flutter with aberrant conduction, or ventricular premature complexes
1270	 with occasional atrial premature complexes
1274	 with frequent atrial premature complexes
1275	 with frequent atrial premature complexes in a pattern of bigeminy
1300	Junctional rhythm
1320	Rapid junctional rhythm
1330	Junctional bradycardia
1400	Undetermined rhythm (Possible supraventricular rhythm)
1420	Undetermined rhythm (Possible supraventricular tachycardia)
1430	Undetermined rhythm (Possible supraventricular bradycardia)
1470	 with occasional supraventricular premature complexes
1474	 with frequent supraventricular premature complexes
1475	 with frequent supraventricular premature complexes in a pattern of bigeminy
1500	Ventricular rhythm
1520	Ventricular tachycardia
1570	 with occasional ventricular premature complexes
15708	 with occasional ventricular premature complexes (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1574	 with frequent ventricular premature complexes
15748	 with frequent ventricular premature complexes (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1575	 with frequent ventricular premature complexes in a pattern of bigeminy
15758	 with frequent ventricular premature complexes in a pattern of bigeminy (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1577	 with couplet ventricular premature complexes
15778	 with couplet ventricular premature complexes (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
16006	Electronic atrial pacemaker
16007	Electronic ventricular pacemaker
16008	Electronic atrial pacemaker (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
16009	Electronic ventricular pacemaker (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1901	Undetermined regular rhythm
1902	Undetermined rhythm
1921	Undetermined regular rhythm (tachycardia)
1922	Undetermined rhythm (tachycardia)
1931	Undetermined regular rhythm (bradicardia)
1932	Undetermined rhythm (bradycardia)
1938	Extreme bradycardia
1970	 with occasional ectopic premature complexes
19708	 with occasional ectopic premature complexes (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1974	 with frequent ectopic premature complexes
19748	 with frequent ectopic premature complexes (Unreliable analysis due to noise)
1975	 with frequent ectopic premature complexes in a pattern of bigeminy
2210	Short PR interval
2216	Type-A Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome
2217	Type-B Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome
2218	Atypical Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome
2219	Intermittent Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome
2230	AV block
2231	First degree AV block
2232	2nd degree AV block, Mobitz type I
2233	2nd degree AV block, Mobitz type II
2234	Possible 3rd degree AV block
2320	Nonspecific intraventricular conduction delay
2330	Nonspecific intraventricular conduction block
2420	RSR (QR) in lead V1/V2, consistent with right ventricular conduction delay
2440	Incomplete right bundle branch block
2450	Right bundle branch block
24501	Right bundle branch block, plus possible RVH
2540	Incomplete left bundle branch block
2550	Left bundle branch block
2630	Left anterior fascicular block
2730	Left posterior fascicular block
3104	Poor R wave progression
3113	Cannot rule out anterior myocardial infarction, probably old
31131	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3114	Cannot rule out anterior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
31141	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3121	Possible anterior myocardial infarction, possibly acute
31211	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3122	Possible anterior myocardial infarction, probably recent
31221	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3123	Possible anterior myocardial infarction, probably old
31231	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3124	Possible anterior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
31241	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3131	Anterior myocardial infarction, possibly acute
31311	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3132	Anterior myocardial infarction, probably recent
31321	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3133	Anterior myocardial infarction, probably old
31331	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3134	Anterior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
31341	Abnormal Qwave in lead V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3213	Cannot rule out anteroseptal myocardial infarction, probably old
32131	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3214	Cannot rule out anteroseptal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
32141	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3221	Possible anteroseptal myocardial infarction, possibly acute
32211	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3222	Possible anteroseptal myocardial infarction, probably recent
32221	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3223	Possible anteroseptal myocardial infarction, probably old
32231	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3224	Possible anteroseptal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
32241	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3231	Anteroseptal myocardial infarction, possibly acute
32311	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3232	Anteroseptal myocardial infarction, probably recent
32321	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3233	Anteroseptal myocardial infarction, probably old
32331	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3234	Anteroseptal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
32341	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2+V3/V4, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3313	Cannot rule out anterolateral myocardial infarction, probably old
33131	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3314	Cannot rule out anterolateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
33141	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3321	Possible anterolateral myocardial infarction, possibly acute
33211	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3322	Possible anterolateral myocardial infarction, probably recent
33221	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3323	Possible anterolateral myocardial infarction, probably old
33231	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3324	Possible anterolateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
33241	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3331	Anterolateral myocardial infarction, possibly acute
33311	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3332	Anterolateral myocardial infarction, probably recent
33321	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3333	Anterolateral myocardial infarction, probably old
33331	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3334	Anterolateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
33341	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V3-V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3411	Cannot rule out septal myocardial infarction, possibly acute
34111	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3412	Cannot rule out septal myocardial infarction, probably recent
34121	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3413	Cannot rule out septal myocardial infarction, probably old
34131	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3414	Cannot rule out septal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
34141	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3421	Possible septal myocardial infarction, possibly acute
34211	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3422	Possible septal myocardial infarction, probably recent
34221	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3423	Possible septal myocardial infarction, probably old
34231	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3424	Possible septal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
34241	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3431	Septal myocardial infarction, possibly acute
34311	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3432	Septal myocardial infarction, probably recent
34321	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3433	Septal myocardial infarction, probably old
34331	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3434	Septal myocardial infarction, age undetermined
34341	Abnormal Qwave in lead V2, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3513	Cannot rule out lateral myocardial infarction, probably old
35131	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3514	Cannot rule out lateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
35141	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3521	Possible lateral myocardial infarction, possibly acute
35211	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3522	Possible lateral myocardial infarction, probably recent
35221	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3523	Possible lateral myocardial infarction, probably old
35231	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3524	Possible lateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
35241	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3531	Lateral myocardial infarction, possibly acute
35311	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3532	Lateral myocardial infarction, probably recent
35321	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3533	Lateral myocardial infarction, probably old
35331	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3534	Lateral myocardial infarction, age undetermined
35341	Abnormal Qwave in lead I/aVL/V5/V6, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3604	Inferior Q wave
3613	Cannot rule out inferior myocardial infarction, probably old
36131	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36132	Cannot rule out inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, probably old
36133	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3614	Cannot rule out inferior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
36141	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36142	Cannot rule out inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, age undetermined
36143	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3621	Possible inferior myocardial infarction, possibly acute
36211	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36212	Possible inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, possibly acute
36213	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3622	Possible inferior myocardial infarction, probably recent
36221	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36222	Possible inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, probably recent
36223	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3623	Possible inferior myocardial infarction, probably old
36231	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36232	Possible inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, probably old
36233	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3624	Possible inferior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
36241	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36242	Possible inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, age undetermined
36243	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3631	Inferior myocardial infarction, possibly acute
36311	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36312	Inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, possibly acute
36313	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3632	Inferior myocardial infarction, probably recent
36321	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36322	Inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, probably recent
36323	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3633	Inferior myocardial infarction, probably old
36331	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36332	Inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, probably old
36333	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
3634	Inferior myocardial infarction, age undetermined
36341	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
36342	Inferior myocardial infarction with posterior extension, age undetermined
36343	Abnormal Qwave in lead II/aVF, cannot rule out cardiomyopathy
40106	ST depression, possible digitalis effect
4011	Minimal ST depression
40116	Minimal ST depression, probably digitalis effect
4012	Moderate ST depression
40126	Moderate ST depression, probably digitalis effect
4016	Marked ST depression, possible subendocardial injury
40166	Marked ST depression, possible subendocardial injury or digitalis effect
4017	Marked ST depression, consistent with subendocardial injury
4021	Junctional ST depression, probably normal
4023	Abnormal junctional ST depression
40302	ST elevation, probably early repolarization
40303	Early repolarization
40304	Possible acute pericarditis
40305	Possible acute pericarditis
40371	ST elevation, consistent with subepicardial injury, pericarditis, or early repolarization
4038	Nonspecific ST elevation
4048	Nonspecific ST & Twave abnormality
40486	Nonspecific ST & Twave abnormality, probably digitalis effect
4050	Tall T waves, possible hyperkalemia
4068	Nonspecific Twave abnormality
40686	Nonspecific Twave abnormality, probably digitalis effect
4136	Possible anterior injury or acute infarct
4137	Anterior injury or acute infarct
4144	ST & Twave abnormality, possible anterior ischemia
41446	ST & Twave abnormality, possible anterior ischemia or digitalis effect
4145	ST & Twave abnormality, consistent with anterior ischemia
4164	Twave abnormality, possible anterior ischemia
41646	Twave abnormality, possible anterior ischemia or digitalis effect
4165	Twave abnormality, consistent with anterior ischemia
4236	Possible anteroseptal injury or acute infarct
4237	Anteroseptal injury or acute infarct
4238	ST elevation
42381	Saddleback type ST-segment elevation(right precordial lead)
4248	ST & Twave abnormality
42481	Coved type ST-segment elevation(right precordial lead)
42482	Coved type slight ST-segment elevation(right precordial lead)
4336	Possible anterolateral injury or acute infarct
4337	Anterolateral injury or acute infarct
4344	ST & Twave abnormality, possible anterolateral ischemia
43446	ST & Twave abnormality, possible anterolateral ischemia or digitalis effect
4345	ST & Twave abnormality, consistent with anterolateral ischemia
4364	Twave abnormality, possible anterolateral ischemia
43646	Twave abnormality, possible anterolateral ischemia or digitalis effect
4365	Twave abnormality, consistent with anterolateral ischemia
4436	Possible septal injury or acute infarct
4437	Septal injury or acute infarct
4536	Possible lateral injury or acute infarct
4537	Lateral injury or acute infarct
4544	ST & Twave abnormality, possible lateral ischemia
45446	ST & Twave abnormality, possible lateral ischemia or digitalis effect
4545	ST & Twave abnormality, consistent with lateral ischemia
4564	Twave abnormality, possible lateral ischemia
45646	Twave abnormality, possible lateral ischemia or digitalis effect
4565	Twave abnormality, consistent with lateral ischemia
4635	ST elevation, cannot rule out inferior injury
4636	Possible inferior injury or acute infarct
4637	Inferior injury or acute infarct
4644	ST & Twave abnormality, possible inferior ischemia
46446	ST & Twave abnormality, possible inferior ischemia or digitalis effect
4664	Twave abnormality, possible inferior ischemia
46646	Twave abnormality, possible inferior ischemia or digitalis effect
4665	Twave abnormality, consistent with inferior ischemia
5120	Possible right ventricular hypertrophy
5130	Right ventricular hypertrophy
5134	Right ventricular hypertrophy with repolarization abnormality
5211	Minimal voltage criteria for LVH, may be normal variant
5220	Possible left ventricular hypertrophy
5222	Moderate voltage criteria for LVH, may be normal variant
5233	Voltage criteria for LVH
5234	Left ventricular hypertrophy with repolarization abnormality
6120	Possible right atrial enlargement
6130	Right atrial enlargement
6220	Possible left atrial enlargement
6230	Left atrial enlargement
7100	Abnormal right axis deviation
7102	Moderate right axis deviation
7200	Abnormal left axis deviation
7202	Moderate left axis deviation
7300	Indeterminate axis
7400	S1-S2-S3 pattern, consistent with pulmonary disease, RVH, or normal variant
7500	Abnormal QRS-T angle
8003	Consistent with pulmonary disease
8100	Low QRS voltage
8101	Low QRS voltage in limb leads
8102	Low QRS voltage in chest leads
8200	Dextrocardia
8304	Long QTc interval
8305	Short QTc interval
9110	**  normal ECG  **
9111	**  normal ECG  ***
9120	**  atypical ECG  **
9121	**  atypical ECG  ***
9130	**  borderline ECG  **
9131	**  borderline ECG  ***
9140	**  abnormal rhythm ECG  **
9141	**  abnormal rhythm ECG  ***
9150	**  abnormal ECG  **
9151	**  abnormal ECG  ***
9270	**  negative ECG  **
9271	**  negative ECG  ***
9290	**  positive ECG  **
9291	**  positive ECG  ***

88
en
years
months
weeks
days
hours
ECG Report
Medication
History
Symptoms
Physical findings
Age
Height
Weight
BP
Systolic
Diastolic
Global Measurement
Technician
HR
PR int.
QRS dur.
QT int.
QTc int.
P axis
QRS axis
T axis
SV1 amp.
RV5 amp.
avg RR
Automatic typification
Minnesota code
Spike List
Type
Positions
(A)
(L)
(I)
Ergometer Exercise Information
Exercise Equipment Type
Exercise Mode
Pulse Rate
Load
RPM
Final Information
Ergoline P1
other
Exercise
Recovery
model
EXERCISE
Classification
Large
Medium
Small
Mini
Cat
(Blank)
Position
Right L
Sternal
Standing
Sitting
(Blank)
Criteria
Tachycardia criteria
Bradycardia criteria
Widened QRS duration criteria
Prolonged PR interval criteria
Short PR interval criteria
P amplitude 1 criteria
P amplitude 2 criteria
QRS axis 1 criteria
QRS axis 2 criteria
Long QTc interval
P duration 1 criteria
P duration 2 criteria
P dur.
P II amp.
0x01	Digitalis
0x02	Beta blocker
0x03	Quinidine/Norpace
0x04	Diuretic
0x05	Calcium antagonist
0x06	Proc/Lido/Tocainide
0x07	Other antiarrhythmic
0x08	Psychotropic
0x09	Unknown
